

Payam Zahedi

DATE OF BIRTH: 26/01/1995

CONTACT

Nationality: Iranian

Gender: Male



(+98) 9216516648

https://payamzahedi.com

Twitter: https://twitter.com/

payamzahedi95/ LinkedIn: https:// www.linkedin.com/in/ payamzahedi95/

Whatsapp Messenger: 92165

16648

ABOUT ME

I'm a Software Engineer that fluent in Dart, Java, Kotlin languages and Flutter, Android Frameworks. With more than 6 years of programming experience. I am very interested in learning in different fields, working on Source Open projects, speaking in technical events and participating in programming communities. In addition, I am one of the founders and speakers of the Persian Flutter Community.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - CURRENT

Community Leader

Persian Flutter Community

persianflutter.com

2020 - 2021

Flutter Developer

Ra Secret Company

https://rasecret.com/

2019 - 2020

Flutter Develpoper

Dropp Technologies Group

https://droppgroup.com/

03/02/2019 - 02/2020

Android Developer

Fit Smart App

PROIECTS

Persian tools

https://github.com/persian-tools/dart-persian-tools

An anthology of a variety of tools for the Persian language which you can use in all platform that dart supports

Flutter Breadcrumb - Flutter Package

https://github.com/payam-zahedi/flutter_breadcrumb

Flutter Breadcrumb is an open source flutter package that can easily create Breadcrumb in Flutter.

Flutter Glow - Flutter Package

https://github.com/payam-zahedi/flutter-glow

Complete and easy to use flutter glow UI kit that help you to create and use glow widgets.

Dota 2 Flutter UI Template

https://github.com/payam-zahedi/flutter_doto2_heroes

Flutter UI template for Dota 2. inspired of <u>Umar Aji Pratama</u> UI <u>Design</u> + Click Animation + Awesome animations and transitions + <u>DraggableScroll</u> ableSheet + created with built in flutter.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Gorgan, Iran

Associate's degree in Software Engineering

Islamic Azad University of Gorgan

Gorgan, Iran

Bachelor in Software Engineering

Islamic Azad University of Gorgan

2014 - 2016 - Gorgan, Iran

Associate Degree in Software Engineering

Shahid Chamran University of Gorgan

DIGITAL SKILLS

Flutter

Flutter / Dart / BloC / Dio & Http / rxDart / Android (Kotlin + Java)
Sofwere Eng

OOP / Git / RESTfull API / Socket Programming / Reactive Programming / HTML / Agile methodology: Scrum / Unit Tests / SQL / Test driven development (TDD) / Python / JSON

Design

Adobe Adobe Xd / Cupertino / Material Design

CONFERENCES AND SEMINARS

Speaker at Persian Flutter Community Event

Flutter 2.0 review

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X4AHaKZOdtA

Speaker at Persian Flutter Community Event

Second Event of Persian Flutter Community

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4E7fT9KX6Rg

PUBLICATIONS

♦ Flutter Navigator Middleware

2020 https://medium.com/flutter-community/flutter-navigator-middleware-part1-9ebc47cea2f2

In this article, we will create a simple example to see how RouteObserver works. In part2, we will create NavigatorMiddleware with RouteObserver. NavigatorMiddleware class will help us be aware of all changes about Navigator, not only a single widget. Also, we can do many other things with this service class like creating Navigator Stack.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Persian

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

| Listening | Reading | Spoken | Spoken | Writing |
|-----------|---------|------------|-------------|---------|
| B1 | B2 | production | interaction | B2 |
| | | A2 | A2 | |